A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A81), 1874-2003; 7; 163.49 Cubic Feet 449 containers. Boxes 652-1076; Document boxes 652-1076.
  - United States, 200; 99.41 Cubic Feet 262 containers
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Georgetown University - Reproductive Biology - Supplementary Material, 1978-1979 (Box 855, Folder 5720)
      - Harvard University - Health Care in Haiti, 1972-1977 (Box 855, Folder 5721)
      - Harvard University - Health Care in Haiti - Evaluation, 1974-1979 (Box 856, Folder 5722)
      - Harvard University - Health Care in Haiti - Supplementary Material, 1978 Dec. (Box 856, Folder 5723)
      - Harvard University - Health Determinants, 1976-1981 (Box 856, Folder 5724)
      - Harvard University - Health Determinants - Evaluation, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 856, Folder 5725)
      - Health Services Foundation - Health Care Conferences, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 856, Folder 5726-5729, Box 857, Folder 5730-5733)
      - Health Services Foundation - Health Care Conferences - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 857, Folder 5734)
      - Health Services Foundation - Health Care Conferences - Supplementary Material, 1975-1976 (Box 857, Folder 5735-5736, Box 858, Folder 5737-5739)
      - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 858, Folder 5740)
      - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 858, Folder 5741)
      - Jackson, Bruce A., 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 858, Folder 5742)
      - Jackson, Bruce A. - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 858, Folder 5743)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Kabir, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 858, Folder 5744)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Kabir - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 858, Folder 5745)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Reproductive Biology, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 858, Folder 5746)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Reproductive Biology - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 858, Folder 5747)
      - Morehouse College - Medical Education, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 859, Folder 5748)
      - Morehouse College - Medical Education - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 859, Folder 5749)
      - Morehouse College - Reproductive Control, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 859, Folder 5750)
      - Morehouse College - Reproductive Control - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 859, Folder 5751)
      - Planned Parenthood Association of Maryland, Inc. - Population Education, 1971-1979, 1981 (Box 859, Folder 5752-5755)
      - Planned Parenthood Association of Maryland, Inc. - Population Education - Evaluation, 1972-1980 (Box 859, Folder 5756)
      - Planned Parenthood Association of Maryland, Inc. - Population Education - Supplementary Material, 1970-1977 (Box 860, Folder 5757-5761, Box 861, Folder 5762)
      - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Family Planning, 1967-1981 (Box 861, Folder 5763-5765, Box 862, Folder 5766-5770)
      - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Family Planning - Evaluation, 1974-1979 (Box 862, Folder 5771)
      - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Family Planning - Supplementary Material, 1968-1977 (Box 862, Folder 5772, Box 863, Folder 5773-5778, Box 864, Folder 5779-5781)
      - Tulane University - Tropical Medicine, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 864, Folder 5782)
      - Tulane University - Tropical Medicine - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 864, Folder 5783)
      - University of California - Onchocerciasis, Davis, 1971, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 864, Folder 5784, Box 865, Folder 5785-5786)
      - University of California - Onchocerciasis, Davis - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 865, Folder 5787)
      - University of California - Onchocerciasis, Davis - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 865, Folder 5788-5789)
      - University of North-Carolina - Population Studies in Thailand, 1966-1981 (Box 865, Folder 5790-5792, Box 866, Folder 5793-5794)
      - University of North-Carolina - Population Studies in Thailand - Evaluation, 1967-1980 (Box 866, Folder 5795)
      - University of North-Carolina - Population Studies in Thailand - Supplementary Material, 1974, 1977 (Box 866, Folder 5796-5797)
      - University of North Carolina - University Population Center, 1972-1976, 1981 (Box 866, Folder 5798-5799)
      - University of North Carolina - University Population Center - Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 866, Folder 5800)
      - University of North Carolina - University Population Center - Supplementary Material, 1975 (Box 867, Folder 5801)
      - University of Texas - Okazaki, 1976-1981 (Box 867, Folder 5802)
      - University of Texas - Okazaki - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 867, Folder 5803)
      - University of Texas - Sterilization Study, 1977-1981 (Box 867, Folder 5804)
      - University of Texas - Sterilization Study - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 867, Folder 5805)
      - University of Texas - Sterilization Study - Supplementary Material, 1979 Aug. 1 (Box 867, Folder 5806)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Food Production Seminar, 1974-1976, 1981 (Box 867, Folder 5807-5809)
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Food Production Seminar - Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 868, Folder 5810)
      - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Plant Stress Conference, 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 868, Folder 5811)
      - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Plant Stress Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 868, Folder 5812)
      - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station - Tissue Culture, 1975-1981 (Box 868, Folder 5813)
      - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station - Tissue Culture - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 868, Folder 5814)
      - Cornell University - Ender, 1976-1981 (Box 868, Folder 5815)
      - Cornell University - Ender - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 868, Folder 5816)
      - Cornell University - Ender - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 868, Folder 5817)
      - Cornell University - Tomato Genetics, 1975-1981 (Box 869, Folder 5818)
      - Cornell University - Tomato Genetics - Evaluation, 1975-1977 (Box 869, Folder 5819)
      - Iowa State University - Food Conference, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 869, Folder 5820)
      - Iowa State University - Food Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 869, Folder 5821)
      - Iowa State University - Food Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977 (Box 869, Folder 5822-5823)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Conference, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 869, Folder 5824-5825)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Conference - Evaluation, 1974-1977 (Box 869, Folder 5826)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 870, Folder 5827)
      - Michigan State University - Bibliography, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 870, Folder 5828)
      - Michigan State University - Bibliography - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 870, Folder 5829)
      - Michigan State University - Bibliography - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977 (Box 870, Folder 5830-5831)
      - National Academy of Science - Animal Products Conference, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 870, Folder 5832)
      - National Academy of Science - Animal Products Conference, 1977-1979 (Box 871, Folder 5833)
      - Oregon State University - Nitrogen Fixation, 1974-1978, 1979, 1981 (Box 871, Folder 5834-5837)
      - Oregon State University - Nitrogen Fixation - Evaluation, 1974-1979 (Box 871, Folder 5838)
      - Oregon State University - Nitrogen Fixation - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 871, Folder 5839-5840)
      - Rutgers University - Crop Protection, 1975-1981 (Box 872, Folder 5841)
      - Rutgers University - Crop Protection - Evaluation, 1976-1981 (Box 872, Folder 5842)
      - University of Arizona - Arid lands, 1961-1981 (Box 872, Folder 5843-5845, Box 873, Folder 5846-5851, Box 874, Folder 5852-5853)
      - University of Arizona - Arid lands - Evaluation, 1967, 1970, 1975 (Box 874, Folder 5854)
      - University of Arizona - Arid lands - Supplementary Material, 1955, 1957-1975 (Box 874, Folder 5855-5857, Box 875, Folder 5858-5862, Box 876, Folder 5863-5868, Box 877, Folder 5869-5873, Box 878, Folder 5874-5877)
      - University of California - Soil Studies, 1968-1981 (Box 878, Folder 5878-5879)
      - University of California - Soil Studies - Supplementary Material, 1974 July (Box 879, Folder 5880-5881)
      - University of California - Wild Wheat, 1971, 1975-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 879, Folder 5882-5883)
      - University of California - Wild Wheat - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 879, Folder 5884)
      - University of Colorado - Nitrogen Fixation, 1974-1981 (Box 879, Folder 5885-5886)
      - University of Colorado - Nitrogen Fixation - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 879, Folder 5887)
      - University of Florida - Cowpeas, 1974-1981 (Box 880, Folder 5888-5889)
      - University of Florida - Cowpeas - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 880, Folder 5890)
      - University of Hawaii - Cigeratera, 1974-1981 (Box 880, Folder 5891)
      - University of Hawaii - Cigeratera - Evaluation, 1974-1980 (Box 880, Folder 5892)
      - University of Minnesota - Wheat Rust, 1974-1981 (Box 880, Folder 5893-5894)
      - University of Minnesota - Wheat Rust - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 880, Folder 5895)
      - University of Minnesota - Wheat Rust - Supplementary Material, 1973 (Box 880, Folder 5896)
      - University of Nebraska - Sorghum, 1965-1981 (Box 880, Folder 5897, Box 881, Folder 5898-5902)
      - University of Nebraska - Sorghum - Evaluation, 1971-1980 (Box 881, Folder 5903)
      - University of Nebraska - Sorghum - Supplementary Material, 1967-1976 (Box 881, Folder 5904, Box 882, Folder 5905-5909)
      - University of Wisconsin - Nitrogen Fixation, 1974-1981 (Box 882, Folder 5910-5911)
      - University of Wisconsin - Nitrogen Fixation - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 883, Folder 5912)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Nitrogen Fixation, 1975-1981 (Box 883, Folder 5913)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Nitrogen Fixation - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 883, Folder 5914)
      - Washington State University - Potato Tubers, 1975-1981 (Box 883, Folder 5915)
      - Washington State University - Potato Tubers - Evaluation, 1975-1980 (Box 883, Folder 5916)
      - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center Arid Rangelands, 1978-1981 (Box 883, Folder 5917-5918)
      - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Navajo Irrigation Project, 1975-1981 (Box 883, Folder 5919)
      - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Navajo Irrigation Project - Supplementary Material, 1976 Oct. (Box 883, Folder 5920)
      - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center - Navajo Irrigation Project - Supplementary Material, 1978 January (Box 884, Folder 5921)
      - Wunderman Foundation - Water harvesting, 1974-1981 (Box 884, Folder 5922-5924)
      - Wunderman Foundation - Water harvesting - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 884, Folder 5925)
      - Wunderman Foundation - Water harvesting - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 884, Folder 5926-5928)
      - Yale University - Trypanosomiasis, 1977-1981 (Box 885, Folder 5929-5930)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Anderson, Kathryn Jean, 1974-1981 (Box 885, Folder 5931)
      - Arnett, Douglas O'Neil, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 885, Folder 5932)
      - Chang, Daniel Kit M., 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 885, Folder 5933)
      - Conti, Eugene Augustine, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 885, Folder 5934)
      - Cross, Nicholas, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 885, Folder 5935)
      - Eller, Ronald D., 1972-1979, 1981 (Box 885, Folder 5936)
      - Eller, Ronald D., 1976-1979 (Box 886, Folder 5937)
      - Enders, Michael Jeffery, 1973-1981 (Box 886, Folder 5938)
      - Evans, David A., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 886, Folder 5939)
      - Fajardo, Ileana M., 1973-1977, 1981 (Box 886, Folder 5940)
      - Galt, Daniel Lee, 1973-1977, 1981 (Box 886, Folder 5941)
      - Harvard University - Politics Institute, 1966-1972, 1981 (Box 887, Folder 5942)
      - Hershey, Clair Hawthorne, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 887, Folder 5943)
      - Huppert, Leonore Charles, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 887, Folder 5944)
      - Kapstein, Ethan B., 1977-1981 (Box 887, Folder 5945)
      - Lieberman, Mara E., 1974-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 887, Folder 5946)
      - Love, Nancy Kate, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 887, Folder 5947)
      - Ludden, Paul W., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 888, Folder 5948)
      - Maier, Robert J., 1976-1981 (Box 888, Folder 5949)
      - Malmberg, Russell L., 1975-1977, 1981, 1983 (Box 888, Folder 5950)
      - Millette, Clarke Francis, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 888, Folder 5951)
      - Peairs, Frank Byers, 1974-1977 (Box 888, Folder 5952)
      - Primakoff, Paul, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 888, Folder 5953)
      - Saints, William S., 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 889, Folder 5954-5957)
      - Schatten, Gerald Phillip, 1971-1977, 1981 (Box 889, Folder 5958)
      - Schneider, Ellen Gayle, 1973-1977, 1981-1982 (Box 889, Folder 5959)
      - Schultz, Richard Morris, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 890, Folder 5960)
      - Soderlund, David M., 1976-1981 (Box 890, Folder 5961)
      - York, David William, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 890, Folder 5962)
      - Zacur, Howard Ardlen, 1975-1981 (Box 890, Folder 5963)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Adelphi University - Humanism Workshop, 1976-1981 (Box 890, Folder 5964)
      - Adelphi University - Humanism Workshop - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 891, Folder 5965)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Daedalus Contemporary Scholarship Issue, 1975-1979 (Box 891, Folder 5966-5967)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Humanities Center, 1973-1979, 1981 (Box 891, Folder 5968-5971)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Humanities Center - Evaluation, 1973-1979 (Box 891, Folder 5972)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Humanities Center - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 892, Folder 5973)
      - American Council for the Arts in Education, 1975-1982 (Box 892, Folder 5974-5975)
      - American Council for the Arts in Education - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 892, Folder 5976)
      - American Council for the Arts in Education - Supplementary Material, 1973, 1977 (Box 892, Folder 5977-5978)
      - American Council of Learned Societies - Scholarly Communications, 1974-1981 (Box 892, Folder 5979, Box 893, Folder 5980-5983)
      - American Council of Learned Societies - Scholarly Communications - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 893, Folder 5984)
      - American Council of Learned Societies - Scholarly Communications - Supplementary Material, 1975-1979 (Box 893, Folder 5985-5986, Box 894, Folder 5987-5991)
      - American Dance Guild - Asian Dance Conference, 1977-1981 (Box 895, Folder 5992)
      - American Dance Guild - Asian Dance Conference - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 895, Folder 5993)
      - American Dance Guild - Asian Dance Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977 (Box 895, Folder 5994)
      - Anthology Film Archives - Video, 1975-1977, 1981-1984 (Box 895, Folder 5995)
      - Anthology Film Archives - Video - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 895, Folder 5996)
      - Anthology Film Archives - Video - Supplementary Material, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 895, Folder 5997)
      - Anti-Defamation League - Adolescent Prejudice Conference, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 895, Folder 5998)
      - Anti-Defamation League - Adolescent Prejudice Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 895, Folder 5999)
      - Anti-Defamation League - Adolescent Prejudice Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 895, Folder 6000)
      - Appalachian Consortium Conference, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 896, Folder 6001-6002)
      - Appalachian Consortium Conference - Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 896, Folder 6003)
      - Appalachian Consortium Conference - Supplementary Material, 1974-1978 (Box 896, Folder 6004-6007, Box 897, Folder 6008-6009)
      - Aspen Institute - Television Criticism, 1974-1981 (Box 897, Folder 6010)
      - Aspen Institute - Television Criticism - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 897, Folder 6011)
      - Aspen Institute - Television Criticism - Supplementary Material, 1975-1979 (Box 897, Folder 6012-6014, Box 898, Folder 6015)
      - Aspen Institute - Women's Program, 1975-1981 (Box 898, Folder 6016-6018)
      - Aspen Institute - Women's Program - Evaluation, 1977-1981 (Box 898, Folder 6019)
      - Aspen Institute - Women's Program - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 898, Folder 6020-6021, Box 899, Folder 6022-6024)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Arts & Cultural Trends, 1975-1981 (Box 899, Folder 6025-6026)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Arts & Cultural Trends - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 899, Folder 6027)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Arts & Cultural Trends - Supplementary Material, 1975-1978 (Box 900, Folder 6028-6031)
      - Association of Indians in America, Inc. - Conference, 1977-1981 (Box 900, Folder 6032)
      - Association of Indians in America, Inc. - Conference - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 900, Folder 6033)
      - Banks, Ann, 1976-1981 (Box 901, Folder 6034)
      - Banks, Ann - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 901, Folder 6035)
      - Bay Area Education - Television Association, 1965-1981 (Box 901, Folder 6036-6039, Box 902, Folder 6040-6042)
      - Bay Area Education - Television Association - Supplementary Material, 1959, 1961, 1966-1977 (Box 902, Folder 6043-6046, Box 903, Folder 6047-6050)
      - Bentley College - Business Ethics Conference, 1976-1981 (Box 903, Folder 6051)
      - Bentley College - Business Ethics Conference - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 903, Folder 6052)
      - Bentley College - Business Ethics Conference - Supplementary Material, 1977-1979 (Box 903, Folder 6053)
      - Berea College - Puppetry Caravan, 1968-1981 (Box 904, Folder 6054-6057)
      - Berea College - Puppetry Caravan - Evaluation, 1973-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 904, Folder 6058)
      - Boston 200 Corporation - Stanton Project, 1973-1976, 1981 (Box 904, Folder 5059, Box 905, Folder 6060-6061)
      - Boston 200 Corporation - Stanton Project - Evaluation, 1975-1976, 1980 (Box 905, Folder 6062)
      - Briarcliff College - Public Affairs Institute, 1975-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 905, Folder 6063-6064)
      - Briarcliff College - Public Affairs Institute - Evaluation, 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 905, Folder 6065)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Dance and Theatre Company, 1967-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 905, Folder 6066-6068, Box 906, Folder 6069-6074, Box 907, Folder 6075)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Dance and Theatre Company - Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 907, Folder 6076)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Dance and Theatre Company - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 907, Folder 6077)
      - Brown University - Ethnicity Project, 1973-1976, 1979-1981 (Box 907, Folder 6078-6079)
      - Brown University - Ethnicity Project - Supplementary Material, 2/26/80 (Box 907, Folder 6080)
      - Burk Foundation for Education - Arts Education Evaluation, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 907, Folder 6081-6082)
      - Burk Foundation for Education - Arts Education Evaluation - Evaluation, 1975-1979, 1982 (Box 907, Folder 6083)
      - Cable Arts Foundation, Inc. - Music Competition Film, 1978-1981 (Box 908, Folder 6084)
      - Cable Arts Foundation, Inc. - Music Competition Film - Evaluation, 1978, 1980 (Box 908, Folder 6085)
      - California Commission on the Status of Women - Equal Rights Amendment Study, 1973-1981 (Box 908, Folder 6086-6088)
      - California Commission on the Status of Women - Equal Rights Amendment Study - Evaluation, 1974-1976 (Box 908, Folder 6089)
      - California Commission on the Status of Women - Equal Rights Amendment Study - Supplementary Material, 1971-1978 (Box 908, Folder 6090, Box 909, Folder 6091-6096, Box 910, Folder 6997-6101, Box 911, Folder 6102-6103)
      - Carroll University - Prpic, 1974-1976, 1981 (Box 911, Folder 6104-6105)
      - Carroll University - Prpic - Supplementary Material, 1969, 1971, 1973, 1974 (Box 911, Folder 6106-6107, Box 912, Folder 6108)
      - Center for Migration Studies - Italian - American Collection Cataloging, 1972-1981 (Box 912, Folder 6109-6111)
      - Center for Migration Studies - Italian - American Collection Cataloging - Supplementary Material, 1977, 1979 (Box 912, Folder 6112-6113)
      - Center for Policy Research - Ethical Preparation, 1975-1981 (Box 913, Folder 6114-6115)
      - Center for Policy Research - Ethical Preparation - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 913, Folder 6116)
      - Center for Policy Research - Ethical Preparation - Supplementary Material, 1977 Sept.-Oct. (Box 913, Folder 6117)
      - Chadabe, Joel, 1976-1981 (Box 913, Folder 6118)
      - Chadabe, Joel - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 913, Folder 6119)
      - Chelsea Theater Center, Inc. - Production "The Boss", 1976-1977 (Box 913, Folder 6120)
      - Chelsea Theater Center, Inc. - Production "The Boss" - Evaluation, 1973, 1976 (Box 913, Folder 6121)
      - Chinatown Planning Council, Inc. - Cultural Assimilation Study, 1975-1981 (Box 913, Folder 6122-6123)
      - Chinatown Planning Council, Inc. - Cultural Assimilation Study - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 914, Folder 6124)
      - Chinatown Planning Council, Inc. - Cultural Assimilation Study - Supplementary Material, 1976-1979 (Box 914, Folder 6125-6126)
      - City College - Gross, 1974-1981 (Box 914, Folder 6127-6128)
      - City College - Gross - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 914, Folder 6129)
      - City College - Gross - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 914, Folder 6130)
      - City University of New York - European Left Conference, 1975-1981 (Box 914, Folder 6131)
      - City University of New York - European Left Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 914, Box 6132)
      - City University of New York - European Left Conference - Book, 1979 (Box 915, Folder 6133)
      - City University of New York - Philosophy Symposium, 1974-1981 (Box 915, Folder 6134)
      - City University of New York - Philosophy Symposium - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 915, Folder 6135)
      - Cleveland Area Arts Council - Education Development, 1974-1981 (Box 915, Folder 6136-6139, Box 916, Folder 6140-6141)
      - Cleveland Area Arts Council - Education Development - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 916, Folder 6142)
      - Columbia University - Humanist and Professional Training, 1973-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 916, Folder 6143-6144)
      - Columbia University - Humanist and Professional Training - Evaluation, 1974-1980 (Box 916, Folder 6145)
      - Columbia University - Humanist and Professional Training - Supplementary Material, 1973-1975 (Box 916, Folder 6146, Box 917, Folder 6147)
      - Columbia University - Nisbet, 1974-1981 (Box 917, Folder 6148-6149)
      - Columbia University - Nisbet - Evaluation, 1974-1978,1980 (Box 917, Folder 6150)
      - Columbia University - Trilling Seminars, 1976-1981 (Box 917, Folder 6151)
      - Columbia University - Trilling Seminars - Evaluation, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 917, Folder 6152)
      - Connor, Russell, 1977-1981 (Box 917, Folder 6153)
      - Connor, Russell - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 917, Folder 6154)
      - Council for Foundations, Inc. - Cultural Advisory, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 917, Folder 6155-6157, Box 918, Folder 6158)
      - Council for Foundations, Inc. - Cultural Advisory - Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1982-1983 (Box 918, Folder 6159)
      - Council for Foundations, Inc. - Cultural Advisory - Supplementary Material, 1975-1978 (Box 918, Folder 6160-6162)
      - Council on Library Resource - National Center Periodicals, 1977-1981 (Box 918, Folder 6163-6165)
      - Crocker, Rev. John Jr., 1976-1981 (Box 919, Folder 6166)
      - Crocker, Rev. John Jr. - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 919, Folder 6167)
      - Crocker, Rev. John Jr. - Supplementary Material, 1977 July, Oct. 27 (Box 919, Folder 6168)